{"qid": "0", "question": "Can you name the authors of \"effects of encounters with field stars on the evolution of low mass semidetached binaries?\"", "answer": "Piet Hut, B. Paczynski"}
{"qid": "1", "question": "Can you name the authors of \"the planetary luminosity problem missing planets and the observational consequences of episodic accretion?\"", "answer": "Sean D. Brittain, Ruobing Dong, Zhaohuan Zhu, Joan R. Najita"}
{"qid": "2", "question": "Can you name the authors of \"factorization of seiberg witten curves with matter from random matrix models?\"", "answer": "Yves Demasure"}
{"qid": "3", "question": "Who wrote the paper \"origin of superconductivity in the weyl semimetal wt e 2 under pressure?\"", "answer": "Jing Yang, Jian Sun, Jung-Fu Lin, Dingyu Xing, Deji Akinwande, Juefei Wu, Joon-Seok Kim, Pengchao Lu, Bin Li, Hao Gao, Dexi Shao, Dawei Zhou"}
{"qid": "4", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"effect of self phase modulation in chirped pulse amplification like schemes?\" ", "answer": "Federica Cattani, Anders Berntson, Dan Anderson, Mietek Lisak"}
{"qid": "5", "question": "Who are the authors of paper \"study of chiral property of nuclear matter through measurements of \u03c6 meson decays?\" ", "answer": "H. D. Sato, T. Tabaru, S. Yamada, S. Yokkaichi, M. Sekimoto, Y. Yoshimura, Masaharu Nomachi, T. Haseyama, H. Kanda, H. En'yo, K. Ozawa, J. Chiba, Hideki Hamagaki, Kazuhiro Tanaka, Megumi Naruki, Masaya Ishino, Masaharu Ieiri, H. Funahashi, Osamu Sasaki, T. Murakami, Satoshi Mihara, R. Muto, T. Miyashita"}
{"qid": "6", "question": "Who wrote the paper \"confronting gw190814 with hyperonization in dense matter and hypernuclear compact stars?\"", "answer": "Armen Sedrakian, Fridolin Weber, Jia Jie Li"}
{"qid": "7", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the paper \"three dimensional flow studies on a slotted transonic wind tunnel wall?\"", "answer": "J. M. Wu, M. K. Bhat, Frank G. Collins"}
{"qid": "8", "question": "Can you tell me the authors of the paper \"influence of cassette type on the dqe of cr systems?\"", "answer": "Ulrich Neitzel, F. Gudinchet, P. Monnin, R. Wolf, Z. Holzer, Peter Vock, Francis R. Verdun"}
{"qid": "9", "question": "Who wrote the paper \"atomic gas in blue ultra diffuse galaxies around hickson compact groups?\"", "answer": "Kristine Spekkens, Ananthan Karunakaran"}
{"qid": "10", "question": "Where is the paper \"2 d guiding centre simulation of toroidal electron clouds\" published?", "answer": "journal of computational physics"}
{"qid": "11", "question": "Where is the paper \"absolute triple differential cross section for ionization of helium near threshold\" published?", "answer": "physical review a"}
{"qid": "12", "question": "Where can I find the published paper titled \"electromagnetic properties of proximity systems\"?", "answer": "physical review b"}
{"qid": "13", "question": "Can you tell me the publication where the paper \"on the bethe ansatz for supersymmetric nonlinear schrodinger equation\" is published?", "answer": "journal of the physical society of japan"}
{"qid": "14", "question": "Can you tell me the publication where the paper \"visualizing color plasma instabilities\" is published?", "answer": "european physical journal a"}
{"qid": "15", "question": "Can you tell me the publication where the paper \"uncertainty products for nonparaxial wave fields\" is published?", "answer": "journal of the optical society of america a optics image science and vision"}
{"qid": "16", "question": "In which publication was the paper \"deep hst acs photometry of the m81 halo\" released?", "answer": "the astrophysical journal"}
{"qid": "17", "question": "Can you tell me the publication where the paper \"pseudo hermiticity and electromagnetic wave propagation the case of anisotropic and lossy media\" is published?", "answer": "physics letters a"}
{"qid": "18", "question": "Where can I find the published paper titled \"projection x ray microscope powered by highly charged ions\"?", "answer": "review of scientific instruments"}
{"qid": "19", "question": "In which publication was the paper \"novel way to search for light dark matter in lepton beam dump experiments\" released?", "answer": "physical review letters"}
{"qid": "20", "question": "Who collaborates with author Hiroaki Kadowaki to write paper \"new universality class of antiferromagnetic phase transition in csmnbr3\"?", "answer": "Yoshitami Ajiro, Stephen M. Shapiro, Toshiya Inami"}
{"qid": "21", "question": "With whom does Robert A. Fesen co-write the paper \"a catalog of ultraviolet optical and near infrared emission lines identified in supernova remnants\"?", "answer": "Alan P. Hurford"}
{"qid": "22", "question": "Who are the co-authors with J. C. Kintner on the paper titled \"the search for the scaling function in the multifragmentation of gold nuclei\"?", "answer": "T. J. M. Symons, M. A. McMahan, Andrew S. Hirsch, J. L. Romero, H. Sann, J. Romanski, Wolfgang M\u00fcller, S. Wang, P. Warren, A. D. Chacon, D. Keane, F. P. Brady, H. S. Matis, Cristina Tuve, R. P. Scharenberg, G.V. Russo, D. Cebra, G. Rai, Renato Potenza, F. S. Bieser, M. Justice, V. Lindenstruth, C. P. McParland, M. D. Partlan, Antonio Insolia, A. Scott, H. H. Wieman, Y. Choi, M. L. Gilkes, M. A. Lisa, J. L. Chance, J. O. Rasmussen, D. L. Olson, M. L. Tincknell, H. G. Ritter, B. K. Srivastava, J. A. Hauger, S. Albergo, Z. Caccia, T. Wienold, E. L. Hjort, Salvatore Costa, J. B. Elliott, Y. Shao, K.L. Wolf, N. T. Porile"}
{"qid": "23", "question": "With whom does Andronikos Paliathanasis co-write the paper \"wheeler dewitt equation and lie symmetries in bianchi scalar field cosmology\"?", "answer": "L. Karpathopoulos, Aneta Wojnar, Salvatore Capozziello"}
{"qid": "24", "question": "With whom does Geoffrey B. Crew co-write the paper \"collisionless internal kinks\"?", "answer": "J. J. Ramos"}
{"qid": "25", "question": "Who teamed up with Keith A. Long to create the paper \"range shortening radiation transport and rayleigh taylor instability phenomena in ion beam driven inertial fusion reactor size targets implosion ignition and burn phases\"?", "answer": "Naeem A. Tahir"}
{"qid": "26", "question": "Who teamed up with Yosuke Hasegawa to create the paper \"hybrid dns les of high schmidt number mass transfer across turbulent air water interface\"?", "answer": "Nobuhide Kasagi"}
{"qid": "27", "question": "Who collaborates with author Xiaoyu Wu to write paper \"cascaded metasurface for simultaneous control of transmission and reflection\"?", "answer": "Xiangang Luo, Jiakun Song, Yijia Huang, Jianing Yang, Cheng Huang"}
{"qid": "28", "question": "Can you name the individuals who worked with Wenzhen Guo to write \"polarization dependence of the quasi talbot effect of the high density grating\"?", "answer": "Chuanfu Cheng, Shuyun Teng"}
{"qid": "29", "question": "Who collaborates with author C. J. Lonsdale to write paper \"radio sources with strong jets and weak cores\"?", "answer": "P. D. Barthel"}
{"qid": "30", "question": "Who is the author of both the papers \"an equation of state for magnetized neutron star matter and tidal deformation in neutron star mergers\" and \"effect of \u03bbv coupling on liquid gas phase transition in warm asymmetric nuclear matter\"?", "answer": "T. K. Jha"}
{"qid": "31", "question": "Who is the author of both the papers \"prediction of coupling length in a rectangular core directional coupler an accurate analysis\" and \"effect of fifth order nonlinearity in refractive index on gaussian pulse propagation in lossy optical fibers\"?", "answer": "Ajoy Ghatak"}
{"qid": "32", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"determination of the astrophysical 13n p \u03b3 14o cross section through the coulomb dissociation method\" and paper \"high resolution measurement of protons emitted from medium energy neutron induced reactions by means of a magnetic spectrograph\"?", "answer": "S. Shirato"}
{"qid": "33", "question": "Who authored both \"a method for extracting light echo fluxes using the nn2 difference imaging technique\" and \"evidence for distinct components of the galactic stellar halo from 838 rr lyrae stars discovered in the loneos i survey\" papers?", "answer": "Armin Rest"}
{"qid": "34", "question": "Who authored both \"dynamical and spectral dirac systems response function and inverse problems\" and \"dynamics of electrons and explicit solutions of dirac weyl systems\" papers?", "answer": "Alexander Sakhnovich"}
{"qid": "35", "question": "Who is the author of both the papers \"density enhancement in plasmasphere ionosphere plasma during the 2003 halloween superstorm observations along the 330th magnetic meridian in north america\" and \"analytic expressions for ulf wave radiation belt radial diffusion coefficients\"?", "answer": "Ian R. Mann"}
{"qid": "36", "question": "Who is the author of both the papers \"low frequency hopping conductivity of random chains\" and \"nonequilibrium transport of an electron phonon hole system in a semiconductor quantum well\"?", "answer": "Melvin Lax"}
{"qid": "37", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"unidentified infrared emission bands in the diffuse interstellar medium\" and paper \"the spitzer space telescope mission\"?", "answer": "T. L. Roellig"}
{"qid": "38", "question": "Can you tell me who penned both the papers \"measurement of the liquid argon energy response to nuclear and electronic recoils\" and \"experimental study of sup 84 ga beta decay evidence for a rapid onset of collectivity in the vicinity of sup 78 ni\"?", "answer": "M. Lebois"}
{"qid": "39", "question": "Who writed both the paper \"association between geotail plasma flows and auroral poleward boundary intensifications observed by canopus photometers\" and paper \"generation and evolution of two opposite types of mesoscale plasma sheet bubbles\"?", "answer": "Larry R. Lyons"}
{"qid": "40", "question": "Considering the number of collaborative work, who is the closest associate of author J. S. Yang?", "answer": "P.C.Y. Lee"}
{"qid": "41", "question": "Considering the number of collaborative work, who is the closest associate of author Himanshu M. Joshi?", "answer": "Ralph L. Webb"}
{"qid": "42", "question": "Considering the number of collaborative work, who is the closest associate of author Mingliang Zhou?", "answer": "Yongsheng Gao"}
{"qid": "43", "question": "Who collaborates most frequently with the author Francois Charette?", "answer": "Chris R. Fuller"}
{"qid": "44", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Veszpremi? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "J. H. Kim"}
{"qid": "45", "question": "Who is the closest collaborator with author Eugene Gualtieri? Closeness is defined in terms of the number of collaboration together.", "answer": "J. Yee"}
{"qid": "46", "question": "Who collaborates most frequently with the author J. M. Hastings?", "answer": "L. M. Corliss"}
{"qid": "47", "question": "Who collaborates most frequently with the author M. Spite?", "answer": "F. Spite"}
{"qid": "48", "question": "Who collaborates most frequently with the author N. A. Hawkins?", "answer": "Robert Connon Smith"}
{"qid": "49", "question": "Who has the highest number of collaborations with author Enrique Maci\u00e1?", "answer": "Francisco Dom\u00ednguez-Adame"}
{"qid": "50", "question": "What was the number of authors Barun Ghosh collaborated with in 2018", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "51", "question": "What is the count of co-authors that author Kriti Charan worked with in 2008", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "52", "question": "What is the count of co-authors that author F. Berghaus worked with in 2012", "answer": "2762"}
{"qid": "53", "question": "What was the number of authors W. R. T. Edge collaborated with in 2005", "answer": "9"}
{"qid": "54", "question": "How many collaborators does author S. Moretti have in 2009", "answer": "12"}
{"qid": "55", "question": "In 2011, how many other authors did Y. Xie collaborate with", "answer": "3012"}
{"qid": "56", "question": "What was the number of authors Won-Seok Chang collaborated with in 2010", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "57", "question": "What is the count of co-authors that author Yuichi Takabayashi worked with in 2003", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "58", "question": "How many collaborators does author A. Santra have in 2017", "answer": "2344"}
{"qid": "59", "question": "What was the number of authors Robert E. W. Pfund collaborated with in 2004", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "60", "question": "How many scholarly papers do Guobiao Mo and Ashok S. Sangani share authorship on?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "61", "question": "How many scholarly papers do K.M. Hung and Trevor J. Hall share authorship on?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "62", "question": "How many scholarly papers do S. Viret and Giuseppe Francesco Tartarelli share authorship on?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "63", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were jointly written by David Sloan and Adam Henderson?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "64", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were jointly written by U. Trunk and Jing Wang?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "65", "question": "How many papers did M. Finkenthal and H. W. Moos write together?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "66", "question": "What is the total number of papers K Horst and George M. Seidel co-authored?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "67", "question": "How many scholarly papers do T. Oversluizen and Erik D. Johnson share authorship on?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "68", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were jointly written by Michael N. Fanelli and Savita Mathur?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "69", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers were jointly written by D. A. Rosa and Irapuan Rodrigues?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "70", "question": "How many papers have cited \"a feedback model for the source of auroral kilometric radiation\" in their references?", "answer": "74"}
{"qid": "71", "question": "What is the number of papers that reference the paper \"the interplay of disc wind and dynamical ejecta in the aftermath of neutron star black hole mergers\"?", "answer": "39"}
{"qid": "72", "question": "What is the number of papers that reference the paper \"scaling in necklaces of monopoles and semipoles\"?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "73", "question": "How many papers have cited \"kaluza klein theory with the lanczos lagrangian\" in their references?", "answer": "39"}
{"qid": "74", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers have made references to \"photon noise from chaotic and coherent millimeter wave sources measured with horn coupled aluminum lumped element kinetic inductance detectors\"?", "answer": "5"}
{"qid": "75", "question": "What is the number of papers that reference the paper \"testing the white dwarf mass radius relationship with eclipsing binaries\"?", "answer": "30"}
{"qid": "76", "question": "How many papers have cited \"vanadium pentoxide v2o5 a van der waals density functional study\" in their references?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "77", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers have made references to \"zn and cr abundances in damped lyman alpha systems from the corals survey\"?", "answer": "89"}
{"qid": "78", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers have made references to \"quantum cascade photodetector\"?", "answer": "31"}
{"qid": "79", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers have made references to \"dynamics of interacting fermions under spin orbit coupling in an optical lattice clock\"?", "answer": "19"}
{"qid": "80", "question": "In \"tidally induced radius inflation of sub neptunes\", how many papers are referenced?", "answer": "106"}
{"qid": "81", "question": "How many papers does paper \"simulated predictions for h i at z 3 35 with the ooty wide field array i instrument and the foregrounds\" cite?", "answer": "61"}
{"qid": "82", "question": "What is the number of papers cited by \"rapidity correlations in ultra relativistic nuclear collisions\"?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "83", "question": "How many papers does paper \"charged particles in an intense plane electromagnetic wave limitations of the nonrelativistic theory\" cite?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "84", "question": "How many papers does paper \"islands in the stream the effect of plasma flow on tearing stabilitya\" cite?", "answer": "32"}
{"qid": "85", "question": "How many papers does paper \"mid infrared interferometry on spectral lines i instrumentation\" cite?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "86", "question": "What is the number of papers cited by \"reducing the suspension thermal noise of advanced gravitational wave detectors\"?", "answer": "13"}
{"qid": "87", "question": "In \"chern simons and palatini actions and 2 1 gravity\", how many papers are referenced?", "answer": "6"}
{"qid": "88", "question": "In \"nuclear structure of 124xe in dynamic ppq model\", how many papers are referenced?", "answer": "13"}
{"qid": "89", "question": "What is the number of papers cited by \"effects of planetesimal accretion on the thermal and structural evolution of sub neptunes\"?", "answer": "75"}
{"qid": "90", "question": "What is the most referenced publication by Andrea Alberti?", "answer": "precision measurement of gravity with cold atoms in an optical lattice and comparison with a classical gravimeter"}
{"qid": "91", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author A.S. Rozhavsky?", "answer": "evidence for a chiral anomaly in solid state physics"}
{"qid": "92", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author Yves Henry?", "answer": "spin accumulation and domain wall magnetoresistance in 35 nm co wires"}
{"qid": "93", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author E. Poirier?", "answer": "shape study of the n z nucleus kr 72 via \u03b2 decay"}
{"qid": "94", "question": "What is the most referenced publication by P. Benaben?", "answer": "results from prototypes of environmental and health alarm devices based on gaseous detectors operating in air in counting mode"}
{"qid": "95", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author D. \u010capek?", "answer": "the thermal emission from boulders on 25143 itokawa and general implications for the yorp effect"}
{"qid": "96", "question": "Can you tell me the most frequently cited manuscript by T. Sekioka?", "answer": "photoionization of 4d electrons in singly charged xe ions"}
{"qid": "97", "question": "What is the most referenced publication by M. Kreuzer?", "answer": "bphzl subtraction scheme and axial gauges"}
{"qid": "98", "question": "Which is the most cited paper by author D.J. Benton?", "answer": "double giant resonances in pion double charge exchange on 51v 115in and 197au"}
{"qid": "99", "question": "Can you tell me the most frequently cited manuscript by T. J. M. Boyd?", "answer": "laser plasma interaction physics in underdense coronal plasmas"}
{"qid": "100", "question": "In total, how many papers has Charles L. Seitz authored?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "101", "question": "What is the number of papers written by author B. Akgun?", "answer": "11"}
{"qid": "102", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers T Grycuk has written?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "103", "question": "What is the number of papers written by author Krzysztof Serkowski?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "104", "question": "What is the number of papers written by author I. Gjerpe?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "105", "question": "In total, how many papers has \u015e. \u00c7al\u0131\u015fkan authored?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "106", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers Yuri. Kh. Akhmadeev has written?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "107", "question": "In total, how many papers has Fernando Parente authored?", "answer": "19"}
{"qid": "108", "question": "Can you tell me how many papers V. Morisbak has written?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "109", "question": "What is the number of papers written by author Miru Lee?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "110", "question": "What is the main venue where W.M. Hamdy and Pierre A. Humblet collaborated?", "answer": "journal of lightwave technology"}
{"qid": "111", "question": "Where did Changyong Song and Hyon Chol Kang mostly work together?", "answer": "optics express"}
{"qid": "112", "question": "Where was the chief place of collaboration for L. M. Pismen and A. Nir?", "answer": "physics of fluids"}
{"qid": "113", "question": "What is the main venue where Albert C. Chen and Y. Teramoto collaborated?", "answer": "physical review d"}
{"qid": "114", "question": "Where was the chief place of collaboration for J. L. Gimmell and L. Santi?", "answer": "physical review letters"}
{"qid": "115", "question": "Where did Nathan J Hoteling and Daniel S. Swetz mostly work together?", "answer": "applied physics letters"}
{"qid": "116", "question": "Which venue did Manpreet Kaur and Raj K. Gupta collaborate most?", "answer": "physical review c"}
{"qid": "117", "question": "What is the main venue where H. Enke and C. Carrion collaborated?", "answer": "astronomy and astrophysics"}
{"qid": "118", "question": "What is the main venue where P. Seibert and G\u00fcnter Werth collaborated?", "answer": "epl"}
{"qid": "119", "question": "Where did Madhi Esmaeilzadeh and Joseph E. Willett mostly work together?", "answer": "physics of plasmas"}
{"qid": "120", "question": "What is the least number of individuals author Yoshiyuki Ichinozuka requires to know to be acquainted with author Hiromitsu Haba?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "121", "question": "How many people does author Marc Andrew Valdez need to know at least to know author David Kaiser?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "122", "question": "How many people does author Lynne H. Orr need to know at least to know author P. Giannetti?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "123", "question": "What is the minimum number of people author S. Jain must know in order to know author B. Iyutin?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "124", "question": "What is the least number of individuals author A. I. Kuzovlev requires to know to be acquainted with author Yoshiaki Nakamura?", "answer": "3"}
{"qid": "125", "question": "What is the least number of individuals author Uzoma Onunkwo requires to know to be acquainted with author Paolo Zanardi?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "126", "question": "What is the minimum number of people author Chris Morton must know in order to know author Andrew R. Lambert?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "127", "question": "How many people minimum must author L. V. Kuhi be aware of to know author Hyron Spinrad?", "answer": "1"}
{"qid": "128", "question": "How many people does author V. D. Chesnokova need to know at least to know author O.V. Herashchenko?", "answer": "2"}
{"qid": "129", "question": "How many people minimum must author B. W. Fravel be aware of to know author Steven T. Rodan?", "answer": "4"}
{"qid": "130", "question": "For a reader of the paper titled kelvin helmholtz instabilities in swirling jets, which paper out of characterization of spectroscopic photoemission and low energy electron microscope using multipolarized soft x rays at bl17su spring 8, double resonance self induced transparency, introduction to the replica theory of disordered statistical systems, the regular structure of shock accelerated 40 100 kev electrons in the high latitude heliosphere, probing long period companions to planetary hosts vlt and cfht near infrared coronographic imaging surveys, diamond based photoconductors for deep uv detection, probing biological light harvesting phenomena by optical cavities, effect of intermediate fluid layer on kelvin helmholtz instability, intermediate phase of the one dimensional half filled hubbard holstein model, the einstein hilbert action with cosmological constant as a functional of generic form would be recommended? Please only use paper titles in your response, not IDs.", "answer": "effect of intermediate fluid layer on kelvin helmholtz instability"}
{"qid": "131", "question": "For a reader of the paper titled generalized mass radius relations and mass entropy relations for components of contact binaries, which paper out of stochastic approximation of dynamical exponent at quantum critical point, binary single star scattering i numerical experiments for equal masses, calculating free energy profiles in biomolecular systems from fast nonequilibrium processes, homogeneous illusion device exhibiting transformed and shifted scattering effect, heat transfer regimes in fully developed plane channel flows, self consistent population spectral synthesis with fado i the importance of nebular emission in modelling star forming galaxies, sub milliarcsecond imaging of quasars and active galactic nuclei iv fine scale structure, optical studies of v404 cyg the x ray transient gs 2023 338 iii the secondary star and accretion disc, angular momentum and the formation of stars and black holes, on the \u03b4 i 1 2 rule in the \u03bb n nn reaction would be recommended? Please only use paper titles in your response, not IDs.", "answer": "binary single star scattering i numerical experiments for equal masses"}
{"qid": "132", "question": "Considering a reader of fourier transform spectroscopy of the swan d sup 3 sup pi sub g sub a sup 3 sup pi sub u sub system of the jet cooled c2 molecule, which of these papers - sum rules for quasifree scattering of hadrons, the swan system of c2 a global analysis of fourier transform emission spectra, a g scidar for ground layer turbulence measurements at high vertical resolution, strongly interacting luttinger liquid state in the integrable model of spinless fermions, nonuniform cosmological birefringence and active galactic nuclei, majorization formulation of uncertainty in quantum mechanics, observation of two species of vortices in the anisotropic spin triplet superconductor sr2ruo4, two species boson mixture on a ring a group theoretic approach to the quantum dynamics of low energy excitations, scattering phenomena electron molecule collisions, new parametrizations of non gaussian line of sight velocity distribution - would you suggest? Please use the paper title in your answer, not the ID.", "answer": "the swan system of c2 a global analysis of fourier transform emission spectra"}
{"qid": "133", "question": "Considering a reader of a lattice study of the form factors a0 and a3 in the decay b 0 \u03f1 l \u03bd l, which of these papers - anomalous softening of spin phonon coupled mode on cugeo3, formation and properties of essentially nonequilibrium polaritons in small crystals seen through luminescence of solid xenon, on axion and familons, a threshold improved narrow width approximation for bsm physics, the colors and luminosities of white dwarfs, string junctions and holographic interfaces, semiclassical treatments of non radiative processes, wire chamber requirements and tracking simulation studies for tracking systems at the superconducting super collider, lattice study of the decay b0 \u03f1 l vl model independent determination of vub, principal component analysis of event by event fluctuations - would you suggest? Please use the paper title in your answer, not the ID.", "answer": "lattice study of the decay b0 \u03f1 l vl model independent determination of vub"}
{"qid": "134", "question": "Which paper should be recommended to the reader of paper metal abundance and age of the globular cluster ngc 6397 from photoelectric uvby \u03b2 photometry of turn off stars? Please select from the candidate list evolution of massive stars without convective core overshooting, soliton solutions in stimulated brillouin scattering, multiple weyl points and the sign change of their topological charges in woodpile photonic crystals, su 3 mass splittings of heavy baryons in qcd, stromgren photometry of open clusters i ngc 6281 ngc 6405, emitted radiation and geometry, polarized quark distributions from scattering of real gamma beam on nuclear targets, the deimos 10k spectroscopic survey catalog of the cosmos field, the chaotic long term x ray variability of 4u 1705 44, enhancement of resonant thermonuclear reaction rates in extremely dense stellar plasmas. Please answer the paper title rather than ID.", "answer": "stromgren photometry of open clusters i ngc 6281 ngc 6405"}
{"qid": "135", "question": "Considering a reader of photoionisation of the 3pe 1de and 1se states of neutral oxygen, which of these papers - non perturbative effect of rotation on dipolar mixed modes in red giant stars, space and time in the modern universe, sz nagy foias theory and lax phillips type semigroups in the description of quantum mechanical resonances, impurity spin texture at the critical point between neel ordered and valence bond solid states in two dimensional su 3 quantum antiferromagnets, braid statistics for the sources of the nonabelian chern simons term, minkowski s object a starburst triggered by a radio jet revisited, bistable systems with propagating fronts leading to pattern formation, spirits catalog of infrared variables identification of extremely luminous long period variables, constructing an explicit ads cft correspondence with cartan geometry, the dielectronic recombination rate coefficients for ions in the he li be and ne isoelectronic sequences - would you suggest? Please use the paper title in your answer, not the ID.", "answer": "the dielectronic recombination rate coefficients for ions in the he li be and ne isoelectronic sequences"}
{"qid": "136", "question": "Considering a reader of role of fluctuations in the linear \u03c3 model with quarks, which of these papers - on the direct correlation between gamma rays and pev neutrinos from blazars, phase transitions at finite temperature and dimensional reduction for fermions and bosons, numerical analysis of the rayleigh taylor instability in an electric field, generalized notion of spin wave for large magnetization motion, polarization dependent nonlinear gain in semiconductor lasers, chiral phase transition within effective models with constituent quarks, multi channel dual phase lock in optical spectrometer, complete quantization of a diffeomorphism invariant field theory, radiative corrections in the varying power law modified gravity, microscopic theory of the two proton radioactivity - would you suggest? Please use the paper title in your answer, not the ID.", "answer": "chiral phase transition within effective models with constituent quarks"}
{"qid": "137", "question": "Considering a reader of physical properties of the quiescent prominence of 5 june 1996 from h\u03b1 observations, which of these papers - book review gamma ray astronomy, limits on the galactic model of gamma ray bursts, topological superconductivity in ni based transition metal trichalcogenides, submillimeter line spectrum of the seyfert galaxy ngc 1068 from the herschel spire fourier transform spectrometer, radio evolution of supernova remnants including nonlinear particle acceleration insights from hydrodynamic simulations, wave based turing machine time reversal and information erasing, statistical simultaneous multifragmentation model for heavy ion collisions with entrance channel characteristics, modulation dynamics and spatiotemporal pattern generation in a microchip multimode laser, hysteresis and metastability of bose einstein condensed clouds of atoms confined in ring potentials, multi wavelength eclipse observations of a quiescent prominence - would you suggest? Please use the paper title in your answer, not the ID.", "answer": "multi wavelength eclipse observations of a quiescent prominence"}
{"qid": "138", "question": "Considering a reader of 2 mm h2co emission in the sgr a molecular complex at the galactic center, which of these papers - wilsonian ward identities, paramagnetic alignment of thermally rotating dust, proposal for a loophole free bell test based on spin photon interactions in cavities, monogamy inequality for entanglement and local contextuality, elliptically desingularized vortex model for the two dimensional euler equations, supersymmetric casimir energy and mathrm s mathrm l left 3 mathrm mathbb z right transformations, dust and gas in the cores and the envelope in sagittarius b 2, energy levels transition rates and line strengths of b like ions, hyperfine structure in optical spectra of cscdbr3 pr3, semiclassical gravitational effects near cosmic strings - would you suggest? Please use the paper title in your answer, not the ID.", "answer": "dust and gas in the cores and the envelope in sagittarius b 2"}
{"qid": "139", "question": "Which paper should be recommended to the reader of paper exact vortex nucleation and cooperative vortex tunneling in dilute bose einstein condensates? Please select from the candidate list asymmetric fermi superfluid with different atomic species in a harmonic trap, classification of kerr de sitter like spacetimes with conformally flat mathscr i, first principles study of the nontrivial topological phase in chains of 3 d transition metals, discrimination of measurement contexts in quantum mechanics, persistent currents in bose gases confined in annular traps, controlled generation of genuine multipartite entanglement in floquet ising spin models, exact eigenstates for repulsive bosons in two dimensions, numerical diagonalization of the glauber dynamics above and below the transition temperature, emergence of kinetic behavior in streaming ultracold neutral plasmas, slow light based tunable delay and narrowband comb filtering at 2 \u03bcm. Please answer the paper title rather than ID.", "answer": "exact eigenstates for repulsive bosons in two dimensions"}
